ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Records 5780/207
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Records
1944-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/207
13.5 cubic feet
13.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
The collection contains meeting minutes from several unions that constituted the district (locals 8, 101, 213, 214, and 215), as well as the meeting minutes of the San Francisco Joint Board and the Pacific Northwest District Council, financial statements of district funds, and board meeting materials of the Bay Area Health, Welfare Fund. Also available are correspondence files of managers of the Pacific Northwest District Council, Mattie Jackson and Katie Quan, files pertaining to organizing efforts; especially well-represented are campaigns at Kong's Knitwear/Elegant Knits (San Francisco) and San Francisco Knitworks in the 1990s.
6766620
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2011
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 16, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
Formed in 1979, the Pacific Northwest District Council included local unions that had previously been part of the San Francisco Joint Board, and Local 184 of Seattle, Washington.
Mattie Jackson, former Manager of the San Francisco Joint Board, served as the first Manager of the Pacific Northwest District Council. Upon Jackson's retirement in 1990, Katie Quan was appointed manager. Quan managed the district through the ILGWU's merger with ACTWU in 1995, and headed the new UNITE district until 1998.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains discrete material from the various locals that merged to create the Pacific Northwest District Council. The overwhelming majority of the material consists of meeting minutes from the locals. While there are some hand written notes, most of the minutes are final versions which have been typed up into forms with sections for agendas, approval of previous meeting minutes, communications, and committee reports. Minutes of the San Francisco Joint Board (composed of Locals 101, 213, 8) are mixed in with the meeting minutes for the several locals represented in the collection and there are also minutes of the Board of Directors meetings.
Records of the Pacific Northwest District Council include minutes of meetings for the Finance and Steering Committee and the Shop Steward Council and Executive Committee, along with general correspondence with other unions and organizations. There is also material of the Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees Meetings, financial and asset statements, correspondence, and benefit summaries.
Another component of the collection includes correspondence files. Kate Quan was the manager of the Pacific Northwest District Council and an administrator of the Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare and Vacation Fund, and her files contain correspondence, meeting information, and reports regarding the General Advisory Council, as well as meeting material and correspondence regarding the General Executive Board (GEB) meetings she attended (1991). Steve Nutter was the vice-president and Regional Director of the Western States Region and present are his reports to the GEB. Mattie Jackson was the first manager Pacific Northwest District Council, and her files contain correspondence, notes and administrative material during her time as manager. Also available are the correspondence files of Myrtle Banks, the Business Representative of the Pacific Northwest District Council.
Within the collection is agreements, reports from commissions and other organizations such as the Asian Immigrant Women Advocates, as well as articles and clippings of local interest. There are files on various garment companies and lists of shops in cities and areas from the Organizing Department as they tried to organize non-union shops in the Pacific Northwest. Much information is present on Kong Enterprises, a company that operated 10 garment shops in the San Francisco area when the owners declared bankruptcy, closed the shops, and left town. Many of the workers not only lost back pay, but also life savings that were lent to the owners, recounted through correspondence, clippings of articles, as well as information on claims and the case from 1991.
Much of the collection is composed of the locals that form the Pacific Northwest District. Locals represented in the records include: Local 8, Local 101, Local 213, Local 214 and Local 215. Records from Local 8 are comprised of correspondence; letters and memos from the San Francisco Labor Council of the AFL-CIO and California Labor Federation (regarding political action, strike sanctions, other labor unions, conventions and proceedings); union business such as minutes from the Board of Directors of the San Francisco Joint Board meetings; monthly meeting minutes from the Executive Board of Local 8; the general monthly meeting of the membership of Local 8 minutes; and special meetings. Records from Local 101 (Oakland section 101-A) are comprised of correspondence; minutes of the regular monthly meeting of the membership; minutes from the Executive Board meetings; and San Francisco Joint Board minutes. Records from Local 213 (Cutters) contain by-laws, correspondence, committee reports, election results, and memos; minutes of the general membership meeting and the Executive Board meeting; and minutes and material from the San Francisco Joint Board. And finally the records of Local 214 feature minutes from the general membership meetings and the Executive Board meetings.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/065: ILGWU San Francisco Joint Board Records 5780/207 AV: ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Audio-Visual Materials 5780/207 P: ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Photographs
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Northwest, Pacific.; Clothing trade -- Northwest, Pacific.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6766620
- Local 8 Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Local 8 Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Local 8 Board of Directors Minutes, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Local 8 Board of Directors Minutes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Local 8 Board of Directors Minutes, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Local 8 Board of Directors Minutes, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Local 8 Board of Directors Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Local 8 Board of Directors Minutes, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local 8 Executive Board Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Local 8 Executive Board Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Local 8 Executive Board Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Local 8 Executive Board Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Local 8 Board of Directors Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes and Papers, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Local 8 Executive Board, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Local 8 Executive Board, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Local 8 Membership Minutes, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Local 101 Contract Negotiations Minutes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Local 101 Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Local 8 Reports [GEB, Special Meeting), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Pacific Northwest District Council- Finance and Steering Committee Minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Pacific Northwest District Council- Finance and Steering Committee Minutes, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Pacific Northwest District Shop Steward's Council Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Pacific Northwest District Council Executive Committee Minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Pacific Northwest District Council Executive Committee (Correspondence), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Pacific Northwest District Council Minutes, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Pacific Northwest District Council Board of Directors, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Board of Directors Minutes, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Board of Directors Minutes, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Minutes, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Local 213 Joint Board- Board of Directors minutes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Minutes, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Board of Directors, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Minutes, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Minutes, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- San Francisco Joint Board- Minutes, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- SF Joint Board, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Shop Steward Council Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Shop Steward Council Minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Shop Steward Council Minutes, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Shop Steward Council Minutes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Shop Steward Council Minutes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Shop Steward Council Minutes, 1991-1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Local 8 Executive Board Minutes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Contractor's Contract Meeting, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Chinese Contractors Contract, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Cuffs and Collars, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Local 8 Membership Forms, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Lilli Ann (ballots for shop delegate to PNDC), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Special Meeting Minutes, contract negotiations, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- All locals, minutes, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Shop Stewards records, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Board of Directors, roll call sheet of officers, minutes and fact sheets of amounts given by Board of Directors, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Local 8 Communications, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Local 8 Communications, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Local 8 Miscellaneous Papers, 1966-1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Local 10, Membership meeting minutes, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Local 101, Membership meeting minutes, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Local 101 Membership Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Local 101, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Local 101, Executive Board, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Local 101, Executive Board, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Local 101, Executive Board, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Local 101, Executive Board Minutes, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Local 101, Joint Board, Directors Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Local 101, Joint Board, Directors Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Local 101, Oakland, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Local 101, Oakland section, Executive Committee minutes, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Local 101, Oakland section, membership minutes, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Local 101, Oakland section, membership minutes, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Local 101, Joint Board, Board of Directors, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Local 101A, meeting minutes, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Local 101A, meeting minutes, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Local 101 (SC)-membership minutes, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Contracting Shop Meetings, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Local 213, By-laws, 1977-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Local 213, Communications, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Local 213, Communications, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Local 213, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Local 213, Minutes, 1989-1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Local 213, Executive Board, SF Jt. Bd., Bd. Of Directors minutes, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Local 213, Executive Board Minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Local 213, Joint Board Minutes, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Local 213, Joint Board Minutes, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Local 213, Board of Directors Minutes, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Local 213,Joint Board, Board of Directors Minutes, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Local 213, Joint Board, Board of Directors Minutes, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Local 213, Joint Board, Board of Directors Minutes, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Local 213, Joint Board, Board of Directors Minutes, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Local 213, Joint Board, Board of Directors Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Local 214, Membership Meeting Minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Local 214, Executive Committee Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Local 214, Executive Board minutes, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Local 215, Executive Board minutes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Local 215, Executive Board minutes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Local 215, membership minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Local 215, Membership Meeting minutes, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Local 215, Membership minutes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Local 215, Membership minutes, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Local 215, Membership minutes, 1990-1998 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Local 294-note, re: minutes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Pacific Northwest District Council, elections, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Executive Committee Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Finance and Steering minutes, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Executive Committee minutes, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Executive Committee minutes, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Executive Committee minutes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Executive Committee minutes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Executive Committee minutes, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Executive Committee minutes, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Executive Committee minutes, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Finance and Steering, 1971-1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Finance and Steering Committee minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Finance and Steering Committee minutes, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Finance and Steering Committee minutes, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Pacific Northwest District Council-Finance and Steering Committee minutes, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Health and welfare funds, draft policy statement, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, meeting, April 20, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, meeting, January 15, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, meeting, February 9, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, meeting, June 3, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, meeting, August 19, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, poll, re: Lilli Ann, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, poll, re: United Labor Bank, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees meeting, December 11, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, meeting, August, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Bay Area ILGWU Health, Welfare, and Vacation Fund Board of Trustees, meeting, February 16, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Vacation Fund Asset Statement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Vacation Fund Asset Statement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Vacation Fund Chronological Cash Statement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Bay Area ILGWU Vacation Fund Asset Statement, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Bay Area ILGWU Vacation Fund Asset Statement, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)